Atlantic States Legal Foundation; Records apap311
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Projects, 1967-2009; Undated; 1; 118.92 cubic ft.
  - Northeast, 1970-2009; Undated; 1.2
    - Rhode Island - A&F Plating Co. Correspondence and Court Documents, 1992 (Box 43 (1-Projects), Folder 35)
    - Rhode Island - Air Inventory Summary Data, 1989 (Box 43 (1-Projects), Folder 36)
    - Rhode Island - Dunc's Plating Co. Correspondence and Notes, 1992-1994 (Box 43 (1-Projects), Folder 37)
    - Rhode Island - Dunc's Plating Co. Court Documents, 1992-1993 (Box 44 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - Rhode Island - Greene Plastics Corp. Correspondence and Notes, 1992; Undated (Box 44 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - Rhode Island - Josef Creations, Inc. Correspondence and Court Documents, 1992-1993 (Box 44 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - Rhode Island - Mercury Polishing and Plating Co. Inc. Correspondence and Notes, 1992; Undated (Box 44 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - Rhode Island - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1990-1992; Undated (Box 44 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - Rhode Island - Miscellaneous and Notes, Undated (Box 44 (1-Projects), Folder 6)
    - Rhode Island - Murdock Webbing Co. Correspondence and Notes, 1992; Undated (Box 44 (1-Projects), Folder 7)
    - Rhode Island - Narragansett Bay Commission Public Notice List of Violators, 1990-1991 (Box 44 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - Rhode Island - National King Traveler Co. Correspondence, Notes, Inventory, Calculations, and Invoices, 1987-1990; 1992 (Box 44 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - Rhode Island - Pamco Jewelry Inc. Correspondence and Notes, 1992; Undated (Box 44 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - Rhode Island - Parker Manufacturing Corp. Correspondence and Notes, 1992; Undated (Box 44 (1-Projects), Folder 11)
    - Rhode Island - Rhode Island Textile, Inc. Correspondence, Court Documents, and Toxic Chemical Release Inventory Reports, 1992-1994 (Box 44 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - Rhode Island - Save the Bay Annual Report and Bumper Stickers, 1991; Undated (Box 44 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - Rhode Island - Toxic Release Inventory, 1989 (Box 44 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - Vermont - Cases, Correspondence, Notes, and Permit, 1984; 1991-1992; Undated (Box 44 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - Vermont - List of NPDES Permit Holders, 1992 (Box 44 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - Vermont - Non-Combustion VOC Emitters, 1990 (Box 44 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
  - Southeast, 1977-1997; Undated; 1.3
    This subseries documents ASLF's projects in the Southeast states, including: Alabama, Arkansas, Florida, Georgia, Kentucky, Louisiana, Mississippi, North Carolina, South Carolina, Tennessee, Virginia and West Virginia.
    - Alabama - Alabama Power Co., Correspondence, Court Documents, and Permit, 1979-1980; 1984-1987; Undated (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - Alabama - Anniston Army Depot, Correspondence, Court Documents, Notes and Permit, 1979-1980; 1985-1987 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - Alabama - Anniston Army Depot, DMR, 1985-1986 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 3-4)
    - Alabama - Cases, Correspondence and Notes, 1987-1988; Undated (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - Alabama - Drummond Co. Inc., Correspondence, DMR and Permit, 1985-1987; Undated (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 6)
    - Alabama - Facilities Report for Certain Alabama/Georgia Facilities Wally Jones, 1986 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 7-8)
    - Alabama - Gold Bond Building Products, Correspondence, Court Documents, Notes and Permit, 1984-1987; Undated (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - Alabama - Golden Rod Broilers Inc., Correspondence, 1983-1987 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - Alabama - Koppers Co. Inc., Correspondence, Court Documents and Permit, 1984; 1987-1986 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 11)
    - Alabama - Lawter International Inc., Court Documents, DMR and Permit, 1982-1984; Undated (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - Alabama - Lexington Fabrics Inc., Correspondence, Court Documents, DMR, Notes and Permit, 1984-1987; Undated (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - Alabama - Polymer Coil Coaters Inc., Correspondence, Court Documents, DMR, Notes and Permit, 1985-1987 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - Alabama - QNCR, 1983 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - Alabama - QNCR, 1987 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - Alabama - QNCR, 1988 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - Alabama - QNCR, 1989 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 18)
    - Alabama - QNCR, 1990 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 19)
    - Alabama - Tyson Foods Inc., Correspondence and Notes, 1986-1989 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 20)
    - Alabama - Tyson Foods Inc., Correspondence and Notes, 1990; Undated (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 21)
    - Alabama - Tyson Foods Inc., Court Documents, 1986-1987 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 22)
    - Alabama - Tyson Foods Inc., Court Documents, 1988-1989 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 23)
    - Alabama - Tyson Foods Inc., Court Documents, 1990 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 24)
    - Alabama - Tyson Foods Inc., DMR, 1984-1988 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - Alabama - Tyson Foods Inc., Permit, 1987 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - Alabama - United States Pipe and Foundry Co., Permit, 1985 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - Arkansas - QNCR, 1989 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - Arkansas - QNCR, 1990 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - Florida - Aquatix, Correspondence, 1993-1994 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 6)
    - Florida - Cases, Correspondence and Notes, 1982-1983; Undated (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 7)
    - Florida - List of All Major Industrial Permits, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - Florida - Florida/North Carolina Municipals Information, 1987 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - Florida - QNCR, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - Florida - QNCR, 1987 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 11-12)
    - Florida - QNCR, 1988 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - Florida - QNCR, 1989 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - Florida - QNCR, 1990 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - Florida - U. S. Naval Station Mayport, Correspondence and DMR, 1980; 1986-1983 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - Georgia - Allied Products Co., Correspondence, DMR and Permit, 1984; 1987 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - Georgia - Cargill Inc., Correspondence, Court Documents and Permit, 1982-1985 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 18)
    - Georgia - Cases, Correspondence, News clippings and Notes, 1986-1989; Undated (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 19)
    - Georgia - Dundee Mills Inc., Correspondence and Notes, 1985-1987 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 20)
    - Georgia - Dunlop Tire Corp., Correspondence, DMR, Notes and Permit, 1983-1987 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 21)
    - Georgia - E. M. Chemicals, DMR and Permit, 1983-1987 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 22)
    - Georgia - General Motors, Correspondence, DMR, Notes and Permit, 1983; 1987; Undated (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 23)
    - Georgia - Kemira Inc., Correspondence, Court Documents and Permit, 1985; 1987 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 24)
    - Georgia - List of Industrial Sources by County, 1984 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 25)
    - Georgia - List of Hazardous Waste Transporters, TSD Facilities List, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 26)
    - Georgia - List of Notifies/ Activities, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 27)
    - Georgia - List of NPDES Permit Holders, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 28)
    - Georgia - Liquid Carbonic Corp., Correspondence, DMR and Permit, 1982; 1984-1987 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 29)
    - Georgia - Magnolia Chemicals and Solvents Inc., Correspondence and Laboratory Analysis, 1984 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 30)
    - Georgia - Ogeechee River Valley Association Inc., Correspondence, Notes and Information Packets, 1992; Undated (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 31)
    - Georgia - QNCR, 1986 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 32)
    - Georgia - QNCR, 1987 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 33)
    - Georgia - QNCR, 1988 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 34)
    - Georgia - QNCR, 1989 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 35)
    - Georgia - QNCR, 1990 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 36)
    - Georgia - Tatum Farms, Correspondence and Notes, 1986-1987 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 37)
    - Kentucky - AFG Industries Inc., Correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 38)
    - Kentucky - AFG Industries Inc., Permit, 1997 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 39)
    - Kentucky - AFG Industries Inc., Preconstruction Review and Preliminary Determination on the Application, 1997 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 40)
    - Kentucky - AFG Industries Inc., PSD Application, 1997 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 41)
    - Kentucky - AFG Industries Inc., PSD Pre-Construction Permit Application, 1997 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 42-44)
    - Kentucky - Airco Carbide Inc., Correspondence, DMR, Notes and Permit, 1983; 1987-1988; Undated (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - Kentucky - Austin Powder Co., Correspondence, DMR and Permit, 1986-1987; Undated (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - Kentucky - Ashland Petroleum Co., Correspondence, DMR and Permit, 1984-1987 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - Kentucky - BF Goodrich Co., Correspondence and Reports, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - Kentucky - BF Goodrich Co., DMR and Permit, 1983; 1986-1987 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - Kentucky - Blue Grass Knitting, Correspondence and Permit, 1986-1988 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 6)
    - Kentucky - Cases, Correspondence, 1986-1987; Undated (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 7)
    - Kentucky - Cases, Company Research Sheets, Undated (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - Kentucky - Cases Not Pursued, Correspondence and Notes, 1986-1989; Undated (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - Kentucky - Dayton Walther Corp., Correspondence, DMR and Permit, 1984-1987 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - Kentucky - General Electric Co., DMR and Permit, 1984-1987 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 11)
    - Kentucky - GTE Products Corp., Correspondence, DMR and Permit, 1984-1987 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - Kentucky - Hall Mack/Nutone Division of Scovill Inc., DMR and Permit, 1983; 1986-1987 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - Kentucky - Kawneer Co., Correspondence, DMR and Notes, 1985-1987; Undated (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - Kentucky - Kentucky Agricultural Energy Corp., Correspondence, DMR and Permit, 1984; 1986-1987; Undated (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - Kentucky - Kentucky Petroleum Waste Inc., Correspondence, DMR and Permit, 1985-1987; Undated (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - Kentucky - Lakeland Wesley Village, Correspondence and Permit, 1986-1988; Undated (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - Kentucky - List of Facility, 1986-1987 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 18)
    - Kentucky - Louisville Gas and Electric Co., Correspondence, DMR & Permit, 1985-1987 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 19)
    - Kentucky - Luther Luckett Correctional Complex, DMR and Permit, 1986-1987 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 20)
    - Kentucky - L.W.D. Inc. Correspondence, Notes and News clippings, 1982; 1986-1987 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 21)
    - Kentucky - Mid-South Electrics Inc., Correspondence and Notes, 1987-1989; 1990; 1992; 1994; Undated (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 22-23)
    - Kentucky - Mid-South Electrics Inc., Court Documents, 1987-1988; 1990; 1997 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 24-25)
    - Kentucky - Mid-South Electrics Inc., DMR and Permit, 1985; 1987-1989 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 26)
    - Kentucky - Newport Steel Corp., Correspondence, DMR and Permit, 1983; 1986-1987; Undated (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 27)
    - Kentucky - North American Phillips Electric Corp., DMR and Permit, 1985-1987 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 28)
    - Kentucky - QNCR, 1986 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 29)
    - Kentucky - QNCR, 1987 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 30)
    - Kentucky - QNCR, 1988 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 31)
    - Kentucky - QNCR, 1989 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 32)
    - Kentucky - QNCR, 1990 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 33)
    - Kentucky - Seagram and Sons Lawrenceburg, Correspondence, DMR and Permit, 1983; 1985; Undated (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 34)
    - Kentucky - Unison Transformer Services Inc., DMR and Permit, 1986-1987 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 35)
    - Kentucky - Union Oil Co., Correspondence, DMR and Permit, 1983; 1986-1987; Undated (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 36)
    - Kentucky - Wald Manufacturing Co., Correspondence, DMR and Permit, 1983; 1985-1987; Undated (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 37)
    - Louisiana - Agrico Chemical Co., Correspondence, DMR and Notes, 1983-1985; Undated (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 38)
    - Louisiana - Agrico Chemical Co., Disposal Study, 1984 April (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 39)
    - Louisiana - Agrico Chemical Co., Engineering Analysis of Gypsum Disposal Options, 1983 October (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 40)
    - Louisiana - Agrico Chemical Co., Evaluation of Construction/Management Alternatives Gypsum Disposal Facilities, 1983 (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 41)
    - Louisiana - Agrico Chemical Co., Geotechnical Evaluation, 1983 August (Box 3 (1-Projects), Folder 42)
    - Louisiana - Agrico Chemical Co., Geotechnical Evaluation, 1983 August (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - Louisiana - Geotechnical Investigation, Gypsum Storage Ponds, 1983 June (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - Louisiana - American Hoechst Corp., Correspondence and Notes, 1983; Undated (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - Louisiana - BF Goodrich Co., Correspondence and Notes, 1982-1983 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - Louisiana - Borden Inc., Correspondence, Notes and News Clippings, 1981; 1983-1985 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - Louisiana - Borden Inc., DMR, Permit and Violations, 1977-1983 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 6)
    - Louisiana - Cases, Correspondence and Notes, 1982-1985; Undated (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 7-8)
    - Louisiana - Conoco Chemicals Inc., Correspondence, 1982 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - Louisiana - Coplymer Rubber and Chemical Corp., Notes and Permit, 1981; Undated (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - Louisiana - Crown Zellerbach Corp., Notes and Permits, 1979; 1981; 1983; Undated (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 11)
    - Louisiana - Dow Chemical U.S.A., Correspondence, Notes and Permit, 1980; 1982; Undated (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - Louisiana - Ethyl Corp., Correspondence, DMR and Permit, 1980; 1982; Undated (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - Louisiana - Formosa Plastics Corp., Correspondence, 1982 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - Louisiana - GHY Energy Corp., DMR and Permit, 1982; Undated (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - Louisiana - Georgia -Pacific Corp., Correspondence, DMR and Permit, 1982; Undated (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - Louisiana - Gulf States Utilities Co., Correspondence and Notes, 1982-1985 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - Louisiana - Gulf States Utilities Co., Permit, 1977 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 18)
    - Louisiana - Hooker Chemicals, Correspondence, 1982 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 19)
    - Louisiana - Louisiana -Pacific Pulp Mill, Correspondence, 1992 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 20)
    - Louisiana - Marathon Oil Co., DMR, Notes and Permit, 1979-1980; 1983-1984 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 21)
    - Louisiana - Placide Refining Co., DMR, Notes and Permit, 1980; 1982-1983; Undated (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 22)
    - Louisiana - PPG Industries Inc., Correspondence, 1982 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 23)
    - Louisiana - QNCR, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 24)
    - Louisiana - QNCR, 1989 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 25)
    - Louisiana - QNCR, 1990 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 26)
    - Louisiana - Shell Oil Co., Correspondence and Permit, 1979-1980; 1982 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 27)
    - Louisiana - Vulcan Materials Co., Correspondence, DMR and Permit, 1979; 1981-1983 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 28)
    - Louisiana - Witco Chemical Co., Correspondence, Notes and Permit, 1980; Undated (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 29)
    - Mississippi - QNCR, 1986 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 30)
    - Mississippi - QNCR, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 31)
    - Mississippi - QNCR, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 32)
    - Mississippi - QNCR, 1989 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 33)
    - Mississippi - QNCR, 1990 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 34)
    - North Carolina - Cases, Correspondence and Notes, 1987; 1991; Undated (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 35)
    - North Carolina - Buncombe County, Correspondence and Notes, 1989; Undated (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 36)
    - North Carolina - Cogentrix of Pennsylvania, DMR, 1991 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 37)
    - North Carolina - Texasgulf Chemicals Co., Correspondence and Permit, 1981; 1986-1987; Undated (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 38)
    - North Carolina - Texasgulf Chemicals Co., Sampling Reports, 1985-1986 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 39)
    - North Carolina - QNCR, 1986 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 40)
    - North Carolina - QNCR, 1987 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 41)
    - North Carolina - QNCR, 1988 (Box 4 (1-Projects), Folder 42)
    - North Carolina - QNCR, 1989 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - North Carolina - QNCR, 1990 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - South Carolina- QNCR, 1986 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - South Carolina - QNCR, 1987 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - South Carolina - QNCR, 1988 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - South Carolina - QNCR, 1989 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 6)
    - South Carolina - QNCR, 1990 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 7)
    - Tennessee - Hazardous Waste Management Program, 1992 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - Tennessee - L.W.D. Inc., Hazardous Waste Report, Permit and Application, 1981; 1985-1986 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - Tennessee - QNCR, 1986 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 10)
    - Tennessee - QNCR, 1987 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 11)
    - Tennessee - QNCR, 1988 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - Tennessee - QNCR, 1989 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - Tennessee - QNCR, 1990 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - Tennessee - Tennessee Gas Pipeline, Correspondence and Notes, 1984; 1988-1989 (Box 5 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - Virginia - Cases, Correspondence and Notes, 1982; 1985-1986; 1992; Undated (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - Virginia - Radford Army Ammunition Plant, DMR and Permit, 1983; 1985-1986 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - Virginia - Pretreatment Permit Enforcement Tracking System Compliance Report, 1994 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - West Virginia - Bright Coal Corp., DMR and Permit, 1986; 1988-1990; Undated (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - West Virginia - Cases, Correspondence and Notes, 1985; 1991; Undated (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - West Virginia - Eastern Energy Investments Inc., DMR and Permit, 1988; 1991 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 6)
    - West Virginia - Hatfield and Henson Enterprises, DMR and Permit, 1983-1985 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 7)
    - West Virginia - Morgan County Commission, Application, 1987 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 8)
    - West Virginia - Morgan County, Correspondence, Notes and Permit, 1987-1989; Undated (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 9)
    - West Virginia - Morgan County Industrial Parks, Application, 1987 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 10-11)
    - West Virginia - Nueast Mining Corp., Correspondence, Court Documents, DMR, Permit and Non-compliance Violations, 1988; 1991 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - West Virginia - PCR Joint Venture, DMR and Permit, 1990-1991 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - West Virginia - Peerless Eagle Coal Co., DMR and Permit, 1990-1991 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - West Virginia - Peter White Coal, DMR and Permit, 1989-1991 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - West Virginia - Pretreatment Permit Enforcement Tracking System Compliance Report, 1994 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - West Virginia - Union Carbide Corp., DMR and Permit, 1982-1984 (Box 6 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
  - Southwest, 1970-1998; Undated; 1.4
    This subseries documents ASLF's projects in the Southwest states, including: Arizona, New Mexico, Oklahoma and Texas. The majority of projects are from Arizona, where ASLF's Southwest Environmental Project (SWEP) worked in conjunction with local attorneys and local community groups, such as, Don't Waste Arizona. Several of the cases involved landfills in Cochise County which were closed or scheduled to close.
    - Arizona - AMCEP, Correspondence, Notes, and Hazardous Wastes Reports, 1992-1993; Undated (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 1)
    - Arizona - American Tubing Co., Correspondence, Intent to Sue, Notes, Hazardous Waste Report, 1991-1993 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 2)
    - Arizona - Ameron Concrete Pipe Facility, 1988-1993 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 3)
    - Arizona - Ansell Inc., 1988; 1992-1994 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 4)
    - Arizona - Apache Nitrogen Products, Inc., 1989; 1993 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - Arizona - Arimetco International Correspondence, 1986-1988; 1993-1994 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 6)
    - Arizona - Arimetco International Water Quality Reports, 1991-1993 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 7-8)
    - Arizona - Arimetco International Van Dyke Mine Summary of Groundwater Quality, 1987-1993 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 9-10)
    - Arizona - Articles and Newspapers, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 11)
    - Arizona - Arizona Sierra Utility Co., Correspondence, 1993 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 12)
    - Arizona - Arizona Sierra Utility Co., Correspondence, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 13)
    - Arizona - Arizona Sierra Utility Co., Self Monitoring Reports, 1992-1993 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 14)
    - Arizona - ASLF and Siegel Bellovin and Kansas Agreement, QNCR and QNVR, 1994-1995 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 15)
    - Arizona - ASLF Membership List, 1994 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 16)
    - Arizona - Bean & Co. Correspondence, Notes and Hazardous Waste Reports, 1991-1993 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 17)
    - Arizona - Blue Beacon, 1994-1996 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 18)
    - Arizona - Blue Beacon Citizen Standee, 1991; 1994; Undated (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 19)
    - Arizona - Blue Beacon Correspondence, Internal, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 20)
    - Arizona - Blue Beacon Court Documents, 1992-1994 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 21)
    - Arizona - Blue Beacon Court Documents, 1995-1996 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 22)
    - Arizona - Blue Beacon NPDES and Aerial Photograph Correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 23)
    - Arizona - Blue Beacon NPDES Permit and DMRs, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 24)
    - Arizona - Buckeye, Town of, 1991 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 25)
    - Arizona - Bullhead City Travelodge Correspondence, Intent to Sue and Groundwater Protection Permit, 1987; 1993 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 26)
    - Arizona - Canyon Portal Properties Correspondence, Intent to Sue and Groundwater Permit, 1989; 1992-1993 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 27)
    - Arizona - Citizen Enforcement, 1993 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 28)
    - Arizona - Clearwater Motel Correspondence, Intent to Sue and Groundwater Permits and Self Monitoring Reports, 1987-1993 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 29)
    - Arizona - Cobre Valley Plaza Discharge Monitoring Report, 1992 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 30)
    - Arizona - Cochise Application Permits (1-2 of 4), 1996 (Box 1 (1-Projects), Folder 31-32)
    - Arizona - Cochise Application Permits (3-4 of 4), 1996 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 1-2)
    - Arizona - Cochise County, Benson Landfill Correspondence, 1982-1994; Undated (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 3-4)
    - Arizona - Cochise County, Benson Landfill Hazardous Waste Inspection, 1988-1989; 1992; Undated (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 5)
    - Arizona - Cochise County, Brisbee Douglass International Airport Correspondence, 1992-1997 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 6-7)
    - Arizona - Cochise County, Brisbee Douglass International Airport Curt Documents, 1995 (Box 2 (1-Projects), Folder 8)